export default
[ { question: 'What is the difference between a hot and cold bed?',
    answer: 'Cold bed: All of your sheets and belongings in the vicinity of the bed remain put throughout the lease. No one sleeps in your bed, except you. Flowernet Crashpads are cold beds only.  Hot bed: Sheets and all belongings in the vicinity of the bed are removed when you are away from the apartment. Beds are assigned on a first come basis so you and others will sleep in different beds each stay. We do not offer hot beds as it tends to be more disruptive, crowded and noisy.',
    tags: 'hot, cold, bed',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '1' },
  { question: 'Is the crashpad co-ed? (mixed gender bedrooms)',
    answer: 'The apartments are all co-ed. We have several rooms that are female only. Let us know if this is something you are interested in.',
    tags: 'people, beds, bunks, co-ed',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '2' },
  { question: 'How many people live in the apartment? How many people per room?',
    answer: 'There are 18 people per apartment. Per room there are 8, 6, and 4 people.',
    tags: 'people, beds, bunks, co-ed',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '3' },
  { question: 'How many bedrooms / bathrooms are there?',
    answer: 'There are 3 bedrooms and 2 full bathrooms.',
    tags: 'people, room, bathroom, rooms, bathrooms',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '4' },
  { question: 'Do I need to bring sheets, towels or pillows?',
    answer: 'Yes. You will need sheets (regular twin size), blanket/comforter, towels and pillows. The kitchen is fully stocked with dishes, tupperware, etc for your use. As well, we provide oatmeal, rice, coffee, laundry detergent, dryer sheets, foil, plastic wrap, hand/dish soap, disinfectant wipes, toilet paper, paper towels and occasionally other goodies.',
    tags: 'linens',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '5' },
  { question: 'What size are the beds?',
    answer: 'All beds twin regular bunk beds. ',
    tags: 'people, beds, bunks',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '6' },
  { question: 'What do I do if I forgot my building key?',
    answer: 'At the front of each building is a call box that you can call search for someone to buzz you in. (It varies whose name you search for depending on the apartment.) Additionally, you can ask on the Facebook group if you cannot get in.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '8' },
  { question: 'What happens if I lost my key / keys?',
    answer: 'We will issue you new keys and there will be a $30 charge taken from your deposit.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '9' },
  { question: 'Do I have to sign a lease? Is there a contract?',
    answer: 'You do not have to sign a lease and no credit check will be done. We do ask you sign a contract that requires 30 day move-out notice to receive your entire refundable deposit back. This is a month-to-month arrangement.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '10' },
  { question: 'How much is rent? When is rent due?',
    answer: 'Rent is $375 and is due on the first of every month. The grace period for rent extends through the 3rd. Rent paid on the 4th of the month is considered late and will be assessed at $5 per day late fee.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '11' },
  { question: 'Do I have to pay utility bills?',
    answer: 'No. Rent is all bills paid.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '12' },
  { question: 'How many storage bins will we get?',
    answer: 'Everyone gets the following: a toiletries bin, a dry goods bin, a fridge bin, and an underbed bin. There is space to hang your towel in the bathroom and for 2-3 pairs of shoes by the entrance. There will be closet space as well to hang some clothing. Depending on which room, this could be either in a closet or a wardrobe closet. Some rooms come with an additional drawer in a piece of furniture or one to two storage cubes. Some beds come with a shelf next to the bed. All beds come with a power strip. ',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '13' },
  { question: 'How much space are we given for our stuff?',
    answer: 'Everyone gets the following: a toiletries bin, a dry goods bin, a fridge bin, and an underbed bin. There is space to hang your towel in the bathroom and for some shoes at the entrance. There will be closet space as well to hang some clothing. Depending on which room, this could be either in a closet or a wardrobe closet. Some rooms come with an additional drawer in a piece of furniture or a storgage cube. ',
    tags: 'space, bins, shoes, stuff, closet, food, fridge, clothes',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '19' },
  { question: 'Do we bring our own towels and bedding?',
    answer: 'Yes. We do not supply any bedding or towels. ',
    tags: 'towels, bedding, bring',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '20' },
  { question: 'When does the cleaning lady come?',
    answer: 'Cleaning services are performed Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays. See more details on the main page. ',
    tags: 'clean, janitor, maid',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '21' },
  { question: 'Where do we empty out the trash?',
    answer: 'Trash chutes are located on the north stairway (except Sunny Tulip where it is South). In between each floor there\'s a square metal door in the wall that drops into the dumpster. A large recycling bin is located on the balcony and will be emptied by our cleaning service. ',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '60' },
  { question: 'What\'s up with the food on the front of the dining table?',
    answer: 'It\'s for everyone! See something you like? It\'s yours!',
    tags: 'food, table, community',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '80' },
  { question: 'Are there any stores in the area?',
    answer: 'Broadway Ave is about 8 min by foot. There you’ll find a Walgreens, a supermarket called Farmer’s Market, along with many shops and restaurants. If you walk to Burlingame Ave (about 20min), you\'ll have a large selection of restaurants, shops, Apple store, and two large supermarkets, Safeway and Mollie.',
    tags: 'location, directions, stores, food, grocery, groceries',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '90' },
  { question: 'Can my friend sleep on the couch or in my bed?',
    answer: 'To maintain a comfortable living area for everyone, no one is ever allowed to sleep on the couch (including you). And in your bed, only you are allowed to sleep there. Friends can stay at the pad, but this is subject to availability and express prior approval. See ',
    tags: 'guest',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '98' },
  { question: 'Can my friend, family member, or boyfriend/girlfriend stay the night?',
    answer: 'At a rate of $30 per night an occasional stay of a non-crashpad person is permitted if there is an available bed. An overnight guest may not share a bed with you. The overnight guest must be someone you know well AND you must get prior approval from us. Any resident who has a guest sleeping in the crashpad without prior approval will be asked to vacate.',
    tags: 'guest, overnight, nightly',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '99' },
  { question: 'I have a comment, complaint, suggestion or issue.',
    answer: 'Let us know! ~ We are always trying to improve but it is difficult to do so if we aren\'t aware of an issue. Please let us know how we can make your stay more comfortable. ',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'General',
    rank: '100' },
  { question: 'Where is the fitness center?',
    answer: 'The gym is located on the first floor of the leasing office, address 1080 Carolan Ave. *Enter the gym through the pool area.* Do not go upstairs into the office or club area. ',
    tags: 'weights, exercise, treadmill, gym',
    cat: 'Amenities',
    rank: '101' },
  { question: 'Is there a pool and/or hot tub?',
    answer: 'Yes. There are two pools in the complex and one hot tub.',
    tags: 'swimming',
    cat: 'Amenities',
    rank: '102' },
  { question: 'Where do I park? Is it easy to find parking?',
    answer: 'A private parking space is $60 per month, but there\'s usually a waiting list, so let us know ASAP if you are interested. Free street parking is on Carolan Ave, Cadillac Ave, Rollins Rd, and in the neighborhood off Toyon Drive. ~ Double check any signs! In some places parking is not permitted after certain hours or parking not permitted over 2 hours after 10am. The parking lot in front of the office is not allowed to be used for overnight parking ever.',
    tags: 'parking, car',
    cat: 'Amenities',
    rank: '103' },
  { question: 'How do we do laundry?',
    answer: 'There is a washer and dryer inside the apartment, attached to the kitchen. We provide free laundry detergent and dryer sheets.',
    tags: 'laundromat, tide pods',
    cat: 'Amenities',
    rank: '104' },
  { question: 'What are good restaurants in the area?',
    answer: 'Farmers Market is pretty much my daily go to where you can get smoothies for 6.99 and acai bowls for 9.99. Le Croissant has wonderful, fast breakfast sandwhiches/coffee. Maverick Jack\'s ([GMap](https://goo.gl/maps/1ZJ3Xbj96DE2) / [Menu](http://www.maverickjacks.com/menus/)) has good, locally-sourced burgers and $10 Tuesday special. Bonne Sante has huge sandwiches that are good, but not gourmet by any means. Que SeRaw SeRaw has counter service small vegan bites and desserts. Mingalaba does Burmese food justice. Rasoi has some great Indian flavors. Limon Rotisserie slangs some damn fine chicken, but $28 / whole chicken breaks the bank a little.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Amenities',
    rank: '105' },
  { question: 'Can I receive mail or packages at the crashpad?',
    answer: 'Yes! Before sending your package, please review the instructions for sending mail. Message us for these instructions. Failure to address your package correctly could lead to a delayed, returned or lost package.',
    tags: 'mail, packages',
    cat: 'Amenities',
    rank: '106' },
  { question: 'When is rent due? How much is the late fee?',
    answer: 'Rent is due on the first (1st) of each month. Rent is considered late if not received on or before the 3rd of each month. There is a $5 fee for each day rent is late.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Payments',
    rank: '200' },
  { question: 'How can I pay rent?',
    answer: 'Venmo, Cash app, Zelle, Facebook, Paypal, Check, Bitcoin, Ethereum are all accepted. Cash payments are allowed by request only.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Payments',
    rank: '201' },
  { question: 'How much is deposit? When will it be returned?',
    answer: 'Deposit is $100 and will be returned after move out, with 30 day move out notice, once all keys are returned.',
    tags: 'deposit, keys',
    cat: 'Payments',
    rank: '202' },
  { question: 'Can I apply my deposit to the last month of rent?',
    answer: 'No, deposit will be held until keys are returned and cannot be applied towards rent. ',
    tags: 'rent, deposit, keys',
    cat: 'Payments',
    rank: '203' },
  { question: 'When is the first month of rent due?',
    answer: 'First month of rent is due the day you move in. Please check in with us for the prorated amount due.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Payments',
    rank: '300' },
  { question: 'How do I get to / from the SFO airport?',
    answer: 'Driving to the airport takes under 10 minutes with no traffic from the pad. Uber/Lyft are $9-15 depending on usage and traffic. Two shuttles operate near the complex. Search \'shuttle\' for more info',
    tags: 'directions, to the apartment, from the apartment, location',
    cat: 'Transportation',
    rank: '300' },
  { question: 'How far is the apartment from the airport?',
    answer: 'The apartment is 7ish minutes by car. The name of the complex is Northpark Apartments. All of the apartments we offer are located somewhere in that complex. The address to the main office (for googling purposes) is 1080 Carolan Ave Burlingame CA 94010.',
    tags: 'location, directions',
    cat: 'Transportation',
    rank: '301' },
  { question: 'Is there a shuttle or bus service to get to and from the airport?',
    answer: '[Crown Plaza SFO](https://goo.gl/maps/X8DYDNUx9Q32) is every 15 min and closest. [Holiday Inn Airport](https://goo.gl/maps/rrDGgW8f9p82) is every 30 min and you CANNOT be in uniform. It takes the shuttles about 8 minutes to get to T1 and 14 minutes to farthest international terminal.',
    tags: 'directions, to the apartment, from the apartment, location, bus, shuttle',
    cat: 'Transportation',
    rank: '302' },
  { question: 'Is there an easy way to get around Burlingame?',
    answer: '[Burlingame Trolley Service](https://burlingamechamber.org/visiting-burlingame/getting-around-town/) runs Monday through Saturday serving both the Burlingame Avenue and Broadway shopping areas and Airport Hotels. [Schedule PDF](https://burlingamechamber.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/ShowDocument.pdf)',
    tags: 'trolley',
    cat: 'Transportation',
    rank: '303' },
  { question: 'Where is the nearest BART?',
    answer: '[Milbrae BART station](https://goo.gl/maps/aCJMVCStp112) ([schedule](https://www.bart.gov/stations/mlbr/schedule) is 1.8 miles north via California Dr. CalTrain available at [Burlingame Station](https://goo.gl/maps/jCtKc1RYobx) and [Broadway Station](https://goo.gl/maps/Zpab8j6KZKw) on weekends only.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Transportation',
    rank: '304' },
  { question: 'Where is the nearest CalTrain station?',
    answer: 'CalTrain available at [Burlingame Station](https://goo.gl/maps/jCtKc1RYobx) and [Broadway Station](https://goo.gl/maps/Zpab8j6KZKw) on weekends only.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Transportation',
    rank: '305' },
  { question: 'Where can I put my bicycle? Will my bike get stolen?',
    answer: 'We offer in-crashpad storage at one of our crashpads for $20 per month. For commuter bicycles, a high quality U-lock should be sufficient. However, bike theft is common in the Bay Area and no lock is 100%.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Transportation',
    rank: '306' },
  { question: 'Are there instant rent bicycles? What is LimeBike?',
    answer: '[LimeBike](https://www.limebike.com) is an app allowing you to find and rent smart biycles scattered throughout Burlingame. $1 / 30 minutes. Sign up now and rent instantly!',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Transportation',
    rank: '307' },
  { question: 'What is move out process?',
    answer: 'Give 30 days notice, remove bedding, empty all bins, return keys. Confirm move out. Deposit will be returned only after keys have been returned.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Respsonsibilies',
    rank: '400' },
  { question: 'Can I submit an official USPS change of address form?',
    answer: 'No. Please do not officially change your address to the crashpad. The tiny mailbox would literally explode if just a few people did this.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Respsonsibilies',
    rank: '401' },
  { question: 'Can I talk to the leasing office / apartment management?',
    answer: 'Since your name isn\'t listed on the lease, you aren\'t an official resident and cannot speak with office staff as a resident. Please do not go to the office or talk to management in regards to the apartment! We have a maintanence request form on the website if anything arises needing attention. ',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Respsonsibilies',
    rank: '402' },
  { question: 'Am I required to do chores or deep cleaning?',
    answer: 'We do not require any serious cleaning from our residents. The crashpad is for when you are done with work and we want it to be a relaxing environment. We simply ask that you clean up after yourself. Do your dishes, put away your belongings, but you\'ll never be scrubbing or vacuumming after others.',
    tags: '',
    cat: 'Respsonsibilies',
    rank: '403' },
  { question: 'Where can I print something?',
    answer: '[Fedex Office Print and Ship](https://goo.gl/maps/XJBYQWbJMpN2) near Safeway in Milbrae will print documents $0.10 per page. Email your document to [printandgo@fedex.com](mailto:printandgo@fedex.com) and you will receive a code to print your document in-store.',
    tags: 'printer',
    cat: 'Amenities',
    rank: '107' },
  { question: 'Is there WiFi?',
    answer: 'Of course! We have super fast internet -- at least 150Mb/s downstream. Network name / password is written on the white board. We have Wireless-N with 2.4ghz AND 5ghz networks . If you have any computer questions, don\'t hesistate to contact Garrett, the tech guy. [FB](https://facebook.com/garrettcholmes), [Email](mailto:garrett.holmes+cphelp@gmail.com?subject=CP%20Tech%20Inquiry)',
    tags: 'password',
    cat: 'Amenities',
    rank: '108' },
  { question: 'Where is the nearest grocery store?',
    answer: '[Burlingame Farmers Market](https://goo.gl/maps/zZLkg6fciP72) and [Oak Grove Market](https://goo.gl/maps/1vPg5UkQtCu) are within walking distance. Other options include a Safeway in both Milbrae and Burlingame, a Trader Joe\'s in Milbrae and Molly Stone\'s Market in Burlingame.',
    tags: 'food, feed',
    cat: 'Amenities',
    rank: '109' } ]
;
